A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Environmental Quality, 1994-2011
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 42221], 1998-2002., Extent: 11 cu. ft. (11 boxes). (Box 1-11)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 January (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 February (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 March (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 April (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 May (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 June (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 July (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 August (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 September (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 October (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 November (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence with Secretary of Natural Resources, 2000 December (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Constituent-Controlled, 2000 January - March (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Constituent-Controlled, 2000 April - June (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Constituent-Controlled, 2000 July - September (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Meetings, 2000 January (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Meetings, 2000 February (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Meetings, 2000 March (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Meetings, 2000 April (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, 2000 May (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Meetings, 2000 June (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Meetings, 2000 July (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Meetings, 2000 August (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Meetings, 2000 September (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Meetings, 2000 October (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Meetings, 2000 November (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Meetings, 2000 December (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence to Governor and Cabinet, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to All Staff, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence to Staff, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence, 1999 January (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1999 February (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1999 March (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1999 April (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1999 May (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1999 June (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1999 July (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1999 August (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1999 September (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1999 October (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1999 November (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1999 December (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Governor and Cabinet, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Groups, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Staff courtesy, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Regions, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Federal legislators, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, State legislators, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies A-B, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies C-E, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies F-H, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies I-L, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies M-T, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, State Agencies U-Z, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 2001 January-March (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 2001 April-June (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 2001 July-December (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Governor, Cabinet, and Staff, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Group, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Staff courtesy-thank you, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Regional offices, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, All staff, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2001 January-February (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2001 March-April (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2001 May-June (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2001 July-August (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2001 September-October (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2001 November-December (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, State agencies, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, State agencies, Virginia resources authority, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, State legislators, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Federal legislators, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Groups and organizations 2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, US Army Corps of Engineers, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, EPA General, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, EPA Air, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, EPA Waste, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, EPA Water, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, TMDL Development Process, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 2001 January-February (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 2001 March-April (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 2001 May-June (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 2001 July-August (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 2001 September-October (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 2001 November-December (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Meetings, 2001 January (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Meetings, 2001 February (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Meetings, 2001 March (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Meetings, 2001 April (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Meetings, 2001 May (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Meetings, 2001 June (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Meetings, 2001 July (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Meetings, 2001 August (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Meetings, 2001 September (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Meetings, 2001 October (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Meetings, 2001 November (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Meetings, 2001 December (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Meetings, 2002 January (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 2002 February (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Meetings, 2002 March (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Meetings, 2002 April (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Meetings, 2002 May (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Meetings, 2002 June (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Meetings, 2002 July (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Meetings, 2002 August (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Meetings, 2002 September (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Meetings, 2002 October (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Meetings, 2002 November (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, 2002 December (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Weekly status reports, 2002 January-June (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Weekly status reports, 2002 July-December (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 2002 January-June (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 2002 July-December (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 2002 January-February (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 2002 March-April (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 2002 May-July (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 2002 August-December (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 2002 January-June (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, OSNR, 2002 July-December (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Volunteerism, Governor's Initiative, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Governor's Cabinet and Staff, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Staff courtesy, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Group-division, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, All staff, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, EPA General, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, EPA Waste, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Organizations and associations, A-L, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Organizations and associations, M-O, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Organizations and associations, O-Z, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, UN Framework Convention on Climate Change, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, EPA General, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, EPA Air, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, EPA Waste, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, EPA Water, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Groups and associations, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Maritime Administration (MARAD), 2002 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Power plants, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - State program, General permit, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Federal legislators, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, State legislators, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, State agencies, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Series IV: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 43155], 1995-2004., Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 box). (Box 1-2)
  - Robert G. Burnley files
    - Correspondence, 2003 January-August (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2003 September-December (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Group - Division, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Staff courtesy, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, All staff, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, OSNR, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 2003 January-June (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2003 July-December (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, International Paper-Franklin Mill, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Regional, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Staff agencies, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, State legislators, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Federal legislators, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Organizations and associations, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, EPA General, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, EPA Air, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, EPA Waste, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, EPA Water, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Dominion Virginia Power agreement, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - FOIA, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Meetings, 2003 January-March (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Meetings, 2003 April-June (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Meetings, 2003 July-September (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Meetings, 2003 October-December (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Weekly reports, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Reports to Secretary of Natural Resources, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Reports to Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Greenwood Chemical Superfund site, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Meetings, 2004 January-April (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Meetings, 2004 May-August (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Meetings, 2004 September-December (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Status Reports, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2004 January-June (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2004 July-December (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, to and from OSNR, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Governor-Cabinet, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Staff courtesy, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Groups-Divisions, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Community involvement, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, All staff, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Director's, 2004 January-June (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Director's, 2004 July-December (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, State agencies, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, State legislators, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Federal legislators, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Groups and associations, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, EPA General, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, EPA Air, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, EPA Waste, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, EPA Water, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - FOIA, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, Board of Directors meetings, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Series V: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 43715], 2002-2006., Extent: 1 cu. ft. (1 box). (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 January-February (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2002 March-April (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2002 May (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2002 May-June (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2002 July-October (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2002 November-December (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2003 February-June (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2003 July-August (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 2003 September-November (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2003 November-December (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2004 January-February (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 2004 March-April (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 2004 May (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 2004 June-August (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 2004 September-November (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 2004 November-December (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 2005 January-February (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 2005 March-May (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 2005 June-August (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 2005 September-November (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 2005 December-2006 January (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 45555], 2000-2005., Extent: .45 cu. ft. (1 box). (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, EPA, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Staff, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, State legislators, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Internal Audit Director memos, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Speeches, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Weekly reports, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 52152], 2006-2011., Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes). (Box 1)
  - David K. Paylor files
    - Correspondence, 2006 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2006 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2006 March (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2006 April (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2006 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2006 June (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 2006 July (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2006 August (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2006 September (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2006 October (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 2006 November (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 2006 December (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 2007 January (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 2007 February (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 2007 March (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 2007 April (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 2007 May (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 2007 June (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 2007 July (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 2007 August (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 2007 September (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 2007 October (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 2007 November (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 2007 December (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 2008 January (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2008 February (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2008 March (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2008 April (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2008 May (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2008 June (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 2008 July (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2008 August (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2008 September (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2008 October (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 2008 November (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 2008 December (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 2009 January (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 2009 February (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 2009 March (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 2009 April (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 2009 May (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 2009 June (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 2009 July (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 2009 August (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 2009 September (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 2009 October (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 2009 November (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 2009 December (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 2010 January (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 2010 February (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 2010 March (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 2010 April (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2010 May (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2010 June (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2010 July (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2010 August (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2010 September (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 2010 October (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 2010 November (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2010 December (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2011 January (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 2011 February (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 2011 March (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 2011 April (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 2011 May (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 2011 June (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 2011 July (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 2011 August (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 2011 September (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 2011 October (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 2011 November (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 2011 December (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Weekly reports, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Weekly reports, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Weekly reports, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Weekly reports, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Weekly reports, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Weekly reports, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 27)